<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:22:54 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Knowledge Proofs: How I Think About Them</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zk-proofs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:22:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zk-proofs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I look at most verification systems, I see the same pattern repeated everywhere: verification is implemented by disclosure. Secrets are transmitted, identifiers are stored, and trust is externalized to databases and operators. From an engineering perspective, this is a fragile design choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zero-knowledge proofs give me a different primitive: &lt;strong&gt;verification without disclosure&lt;/strong&gt;. Not as a policy decision, but as a cryptographic guarantee. While this particular blog is meant to be an introduction to ZKPS, I&amp;rsquo;ll post followups where I will go in deatil into implementation, the tech behind it and real world use-cases.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m &lt;strong&gt;Sudhanshu Bhardwaj&lt;/strong&gt;, a Computer Science and Systems Engineering undergraduate with a strong focus on &lt;strong&gt;backend systems, security, and applied cryptography&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My work sits at the intersection of &lt;strong&gt;systems engineering, cybersecurity, and infrastructure-level problem solving&lt;/strong&gt;. I’m interested in how real systems fail, how they’re exploited, and how to design them to fail less often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve led and built security-focused initiatives at the student and project level — from organizing large-scale Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions to developing tools for vulnerability analysis, identity misuse detection, and legacy system auditing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
